

# SANA VALLIMOHMED BLOCH

### CONTACT

815, Swadhiyay mandal road, Opp. nistha park society, Killa pardi, valsad Gujarat. 396125

Mobile: 9426568026 sanabloch1991@gmail.com

#### **EDUCATION**

#### **ICAI**

I ACHIEVED 56.5% IN THE IPCC GROUP-1 EXAMINATION AND 55.67 % IN THE IPCC GROUP-2 EXAMINATION.

I HAVE SECURED 62% IN CPT EXAMINATION

#### Saurashtra university

I HAVE SECURED 71.71% IN FINAL YEAR B.COM EXAMINATION IN MARCH,2012

## **SKILLS**

COMPLETED TRAINING IN INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY, ORIENTATION AND GENERAL MANAGEMENT COMMUNICATION SKILLS BASIC AS WELL AS PRACTICAL KNOWLEDGE OF MS-OFFICE AND TALLY. BASIC AS WELL AS PRACTICAL KNOWLEDGE OF GAAP, RECORDING AND REPORTING ACCOUNTING INFORMATION. BASIC AS WELL AS PRACTICAL KNOWLEDGE OF IFRS, IND-AS AND GAAP, RECORDING AND REPORTING ACCOUNTING INFORMATION.

## **ACCOMPLISHMENTS**

Academically procured rank in college.

Awarded as best presentation skills in relation to strong command over documentation, management and presentation.

## LANGUAGES

HAVING PROFICIENCY IN ENGLISH, HINDI, URDU AND GUJARATI

NATIONALITY: INDIAN

MARITAL STATUS: MARRIED

# **Professional Summary**

Resourceful accounting professional with more than 5 years of experience in AUDIT ASSURANCE and ACCOUNTING and TAXATION abilities. Productive Articled Assistant skilled in organizing and managing multiple projects and assignments with the capacity to set priorities and meet deadlines. Familiarity with basic accounting principles to analyze and manage a variety of data. Handles confidential information with discretion. Hardworking and a passionate job seeker with strong organizational skills eager to secure entry-level Accounting Assistant position. Ready to help the team achieve company goals.

## **WORK HISTORY**

# **CA Firm. India/ Accounts Assistant**

Apr 2015 - PRESENT

- Preparing and reviewing final accounts of self-employed entities, employees and partnership firms. Also provided income tax return services along with bookkeeping services as well
- Managed invoices, refunds and returns.
- Reconciled all company accounts, including credit cards and expenses.
- Prepared Excel spreadsheets to track banking transactions and financial performance.
- Supported preparation for the annual audit process.
- Completed financial reports for management and stakeholders.
- Produced accurate general ledger entries with the help of different accounting software like tally and QuickBooks.

## **B.H.VYAS & Co. / ARTICLE TRAINEE**

Apr 2014- Apr 2015, Jamnagar, India

- AUDIT ASSURANCE, ACCOUNTING AND TAXATION
- HELPED IN CONDUCTING STATUTORY AUDITS, TAX AUDIT OF LARGE AND SMALL SCALE INDUSTRIES AND ALSO INTERNAL AUDITS OF INDUSTRIES
- ALSO DID ASSESSMENT PROCEDURES OF VARIOUS ENTITIES

- FREELANCER SERVICES
- PREPARING AND REVIEWING OF FINAL ACCOUNTS OF SELF EMPLOYED EMPLOYEES AND ALSO PARTNERSHIP FIRM
- ALSO PROVIDED INCOME TAX RETURNS SERVICES ALONG WITH BOOK KEEPING.

# **BRS & ASSOCIATES/ ARTICLE TRAINEE**

Apr 2012- Apr 2014, Jamnagar, India

- AUDIT ASSURANCE, ACCOUNTING AND TAXATION
- HELPED IN CONDUCTING STATUTORY AUDITS, TAX AUDIT OF LARGE AND SMALL SCALE INDUSTRIES
- INTERNAL AUDITS OF CO- OPERATIVE STORE AND HOTEL INDUSTRY.
- CONCURRENT AUDIT OF CHARITABLE TRUST ENGAGED IN EDUCATIONAL ACTIVITIES
- CONDUCTED BRANCH WISE BANK AUDIT OF NATIONALIZED BANKS